Guide to the Goodwin J. (Goodwin Jess) Knight Papers, 1896-1988 (inclusive), 1946-1970 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Printed Reference Material
  - Subseries 2. Governor's Speeches
    - Sub-subseries 11. Speeches, 1954 Aug
      - Mrs. Virginia Knight -- National Military Order of the Purple Heart8-21-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-171
      - AFL Convention8-23-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-172
      - International Order of the BLUE GOOSE (Insurance) Governor represented by Mr. Frank Creede8-25-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-173
      - San Francisco International Airport8-27-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-174
      - Shasta County Fair8-27-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-175
        Redding
      - Southern Pacific Co. Annual Picnic (Merle Jennings' retirement--Scroll presented)8-28-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-176
      - Pro America (Governor represented by Mr. Cyril Magnin)8-28-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-177
      - Nevada County Fair8-28-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-178
        Grass Valley
      - Political speech8-31-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-179; 15 items
    - Sub-subseries 12. Speeches, 1954 Sept
      - Opening Ceremonies, California State Fair9-2-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-180; (green sheet)
      - Letter for Time Capsule, California State Fair9-2-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-181
      - Brief talks at several State Fair Appearances9/2-12/54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-182; (not rec'd)
      - Sacramento Women's Council Luncheon, State Fair9-3-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-183
      - Sacramento Host Breakfast9-4-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-184
      - 13th Biennial National Japanese American Citizens League9-6-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-185
      - Labor and Management Dinner9-7-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-186
      - Civic Auditorium Speech9-7-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-187
      - East Los Angeles Community Fair9-8-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-188
        East Los Angeles
      - Legislative Service Conference9-10-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-189
      - El Dorado County Fair9-10-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-190
        Placerville
      - I Am An American Day9-12-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-191
      - Jewish Tercentenary Celebration9-12-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-192
      - Mare Island Centennial Celebration9-16-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-193
      - California's Narcotics Disaster9-17-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-194
      - Associated Sportsmen of California9-18-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-195
      - Statement (Press release) re Associated Sportsment meeting9-17-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-195-A
      - National Association for Advancement of Colored People9-19-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-196
      - Sepulveda Freeway Ground-Breaking ceremonies9-20-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-197
        Santa Monica
      - American Federation of Labor Convention9-20-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-198
      - Extemporaneous9-21-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-199; 36 items
        Covina area
      - Southern Council of Conservation Clubs9-22-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-200
      - El Monte Freeway9-22-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-201
        El Monte
      - Untitled, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-202/3
      - Tulare County Fair9-24-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-204
        Tulare
      - Madera District Fair9-25-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-205
        Madera
      - Reedley Ninth Annual Fiesta9-25-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-206
        Reedley
      - Hatfield Auditorium Dedication9-25-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-207
      - Contra Costa County Campaign Kick-Off9-26-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-208
      - Walnut Creek Festival9-26-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-209
      - California State Firemen's Association (Governor's Message read by Chief Yockers)9-27-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-210
        Monterey
      - Untitled, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-210A
      - Governor's Committee on Children and Youth9-28-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-211
      - Delano Armory Dedication9-29-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-212
        Delano
      - Bakersfield Armory Dedication9-29-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-213
      - Completion Ceremonies, Joint Apprenticeship Committees Dinner9-30-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-214
        Anahelm
    - Sub-subseries 13. Speeches, 1954 Oct
      - Women's Club (Agriculture Speech)10-1-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-215
        Banning
      - Los Angeles County Federation of Womens Clubs (Mental Hygiene talk)10-4-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-216
      - Anniversary Address10-5-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-217
        Bellflower
      - Traffic Safety Conference10-7-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-218
      - Traffic Safety Council, Teen-Agers Division10-7-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-219
      - Civil Defense Conference10-7-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-220
      - Fresno District Fair10-9-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-221
      - Italian-American Federation of the East Bay10-10-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-222
        Cakland
      - Columbus Day Parade10-10-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-223
      - All Industry Luncheon (Insurance)10-11-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-224
      - Women's Fashion Show (Talk on mentally retarded children)10-11-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-225
      - California Real Estate Association 50th Convention10-12-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-226
      - California Trailer Park Association 10th Annual Convention10-12-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-227
        Berkeley
      - Sertoma Club Luncheon (Talk on CVP and Water)10-14-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-228
      - Veterans Memorial Auditorium10-15-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-229; (Political speech)
        Culver City
      - Laundry Workers, Local #2610-15-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-230; (Telephone call to)
      - San Diego Square-Dancing Association10-16-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-231
      - Re-Dedication of Oakland City Park10-18-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-232
      - Grand Chapter, Eastern Star10-18-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-233
      - What California Does for its Veterans - Veterans of Foreign Wars10-20-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-234; 20 items (41 total #)
        Anglewood
      - League of California Cities Convention10-20-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-235
      - Redondo Beach Chamber of Commerce10-20-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-236; (Talk on State Parks, Recreation, Water Resources)
        Redondo Beach
      - California State Builders Exchange10-21-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-237
      - Associated District Newspapers Creater Los Angeles Press Club10-21-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-238; (Employment talk)
      - Riverside Campus Dedication10-22-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-239
      - Los Angeles Valley Junior College Homecoming (Education)10-22-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-240
        Van Nuys
      - Red Feather Luncheon10-22-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-241
        Burbank
      - San Fernando Valley Chambers of Commerce10-22-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-242
        Studio City
      - Redwood Empire Association Governor's Dinner10-23-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-243
        Sonoma
      - American Federation of Labor10-25-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-244
      - Santa Clara & San Mateo Counties' appearances10-25-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-245
      - California Medical Facility Dedication10-26-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-246
        Vacaville
      - Contra Costa County Taxpayers Association10-26-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-247
        Danville
      - Richmond-San Rafael Bridge10-26-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-248
        Richmond
      - Miss America Homecoming10-27-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-249
      - Long Beach Harbor Freeway10-29-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-250
      - Sierra Madre Civic Group Breakfast (Education talk)10-30-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-251
        Sierra Madre
      - Italo-American Voters, Inc.10-30-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-252
      - Lynwood Police Officers Relief & Welfare Association10-31-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-253; (polio work)
      - B'nai B'rith award to Danny ´Thomas10-31-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-254
      - Republican Rally phone call---10-31-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-255; 21 items
        Crescent City
    - Sub-subseries 14. Speeches, 1954 Nov
      - Structural Clay Products Institute (Edgar Hervey represented the Governor)11-8-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-256
        Coronado
      - Ebell Club (Extemporaneous speech)11-18-54, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 4-257
      - National Association of State Savings and Loan Supervisors, 15th Convention (Gerald S. Levin represented the Governor.)11-21-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-258
      - Billy Graham Meeting11-28-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-259
    - Sub-subseries 15. Speeches, 1954 Dec
      - Dedication of Hyatt House, Los Angeles International Airport12-2-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-260
      - California Press Association12-4-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-260-A
      - Interview with Drew Pearson12-5-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-261
      - 45th Western Forestry Conference, Fairmont Hotel12-8-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-262
      - Governor's Conference on Narcotics12-13-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-263
      - Governor Merriam's Dinner12-17-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-263-A
      - Mercy Hospital Dedication12-19-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-264
      - Christmas Carols, Capitol Retunda12-21-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-265
      - Ground-breaking Ceremony, Sacramento-Lodi Freeway12-21-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-266
      - Christmas Party at Preston School (Gov. did not attend)12-21-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-267; Background material only. No speech copies.)
        Ione
      - Blind Workers Christmas Party12-23-54, Accession no. M0244; File No. 4-268; Background material only. No speech copies.)
    - Sub-subseries 16. Speeches, 1955 Jan
      - Tournament of Roses1-1-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-1
        (* No prepared talk.)
      - East-West Football Game1-1-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-2
      - Sunday Desk Program, KROY1-2-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-3
      - Inaugural Ceremony, and Message to the California State Legislature1-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-4
      - Sacramento Labor Council Dinner1-4-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-5
      - Church of God Conference1-5-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-6
      - Automobile Dealers of Chicago1-13-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-7
        Chicago, Ill.
      - Executives Club of Chicago1-14-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-8
      - California Federation of Republican Women1-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-9
        San Jose
      - American Legion Post Dinner for Seaborn P. Collins, Jr. National Commander1-7-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-10
      - County Assessors of California, Massage for Publication1-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-11; (* No prepared talk.)
      - McClatchy Farm Review, KFBK Broadcast1-8-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-12
      - Assemblyman Don Doyle's talk to Chamber of Commerce1-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-13
      - Agricultural Aircraft Association, Inc., 5th Convention1-20-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-14
      - County Treasurers Dinner1-20-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-15
      - National Resources Conference1-24-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-16
      - General MacArthur's 75th Birthday1-26-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-17
      - California State, County and Municipal Purchasing Agents' Association1-27-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-18; 11 items
      - Kenyon J. Scudder Retirement Dinner2-1-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-19
        (* Background material only.)
      - County Supervisors Association2-2-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-20
      - Paul Scharrenberg Retirement2-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-21; (presentation of Scroll) (* Background material only.)
      - California State Industrial Safety Conference2-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-22
      - Camp Pendleton2-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-23
        Camp Pendleton
      - National Association of Soil Conservation2-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-24
      - International Automobile Show2-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-25
      - California Motor Transport Association Convention2-3-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-26
      - California Newspaper Publishers Association Dinner2-4-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-27
      - Petaluma City Hall Dedication2-5-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-28
      - St. Helena City Hall Dedication2-5-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-29
        St. Helena
      - San Francisco Bar Association2-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-30
      - State Chamber of Commerce2-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-31
      - Law Alumni of Los Angeles2-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-32
      - W. Lansing Rothschild Scroll2-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-33
      - Lincoln Day Dinner2-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-34
      - Lincoln Day Dinner2-12-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-35
      - Number omitted inadvertently), Accession no. M0244; Speech No. (5-36)
        Seattle, Wash.
      - YMCA Model Legislature2-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-37
      - California Lathing & Plastering Contractors2-18-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-38
      - McClellan Field Dining-In Night2-18-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-39; 19 items
      - California State Chamber of Commerce, meeting on SMOG2-21-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-40
      - Americanization Night, Elks Club2-23-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-40-A
      - Manufacturers Association2-25-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-41
      - Republican State Central Committee2-26-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-42
      - Jewish Community Tercentenary Exhibit in State Capitol2-28-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-43
      - Sacramento Junior College Assembly3-2-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-44; 8 items
        Background material only. No talk prepared.
      - Republic Women's Club of Sacramento County3-4-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-45; 8 items
      - Sacramento Women's Council3-7-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-46; 8 items
      - Berkeley Rotary Club3-9-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-47
      - Girl Scouts 43rd Anniversary3-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-48; 8 items (Mr. Babich represented Governor) Background material only. No talk prepared.
      - California Association of Insurance Agents3-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-49; 8 items
      - Bill Fisher--Dinner Honoring.3-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-50; 8 items
        (Governor made a phone call to him during the dinner hour.) Background material only. No talk prepared.
      - Annual Review of Naval Air Reserve3-12-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-51; 8 items
      - Governor's Luncheon for Labor Leaders3-14-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-51-A
      - Classroom Teachers Association3-15-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-52; 8 items
        (not recd)(Mr. Babich represented Governor)
      - First Marine Division Returned from Korea3-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-53
      - Opening of National Orange Show3-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-54; 8 items
      - California Republican State Committee Dinner3-19-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-55
        8 items
      - St. Patrick's Day Parade3-20-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-56; 8 items
        Background material only. No talk prepared
      - California State Sheriffs' Association Convention3-23-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-57; 8 items
      - Western Interstate Conference on Mental Health3-25-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-58
      - McClellan Field Welcome Home Ceremony (Mr. Babich rep. Governor)3-26-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-59
      - Dedication of Santa Barbara College3-28-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-60
        Goleta
      - State Personnel Building Cornerstone CeremonyApril 1, 1955Sacramento, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-61
      - Conelrad, Southern California Broadcasting Association Meeting4-1-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-62; (Mr. Martin rep. Governor) No prepared talk; background material only.
        Hamilton AFBase
      - Sons of Italy Dinner4-4-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-63
      - Governor's Committee on Ship Construction and Ship Repair4-13-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-64
      - California State Conference of Painters, A.F. of L.4-15-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-65
      - Commonwealth Club Speech4-15-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-66
      - Cal-Aggie Picnic Day4-16-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-67
        Davis
      - Dedication of Dwight D. Eisenhower Barracks, Veterans Home4-18-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-68; (Mr. Russell rep. Governor)
      - Doolittle Raid 13th Anniversary Dinner4-18-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-69
      - State Men's and Women's Club Joint Luncheon4-20-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-70
      - California Rural Firemen's Association4-23-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-71
        East Vallejo
      - El Dorado County Chamber of Commerce Breakfast4-27-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-72
      - Sacramento State College Assembly4-28-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-73; 11 items
        No prepared talk; background material only.
      - Conference of GovernorsMay 2-3,1, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-74
        No prepared talk. Background material only.
        Washington, D.C.
      - Labor group meeting5-4-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-75
        Philadelphia
      - Gridiron Club5-7-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-76
      - Long Beach State College5-7-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-77
        (Lt. Gov. Powers rep. GJK)
      - Lincoln Christian Center Building Fund Kick-Off Dinner5-9-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-78
      - Retirement Dinner for Archie Mooney (Governor sent Scroll)5-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-79
        Eureka
      - Savings Bond Meeting5-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-79-A
      - Aluminum Association Convention5-11-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-80
        Pebble Beach
      - Dedication of Elvas Freeway5-12-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-81
      - Phi Alpha Delta meeting5-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-82
        Stanford Univ.
      - Ford Motor Plant Dedcation5-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-83
        Milpitas
      - League of Women Voters5-18-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-84
      - Peace Officers Association5-19-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-85
      - California State Bar Board of Governors5-19-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-86
      - 7th Annual Hesperia Day5-29-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-87; (Russell Mather rep. GJK)
        Hesperia
      - California Chiropractic Asso. Annual Convention (N. J. Morrisey representing Governor Knight)5-29-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-88
      - Folk Dance Festival5-29-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-89
      - Hank Thornley Broadcast5-29-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-89-A
      - Memorial Day5-30-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-90
      - Memorial Day5-30-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-91; 9 items
      - National League of American PenwomenJune 3, 1955, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-92
        (Mrs. Zimmerman rep. Governor)
      - Nimbus Dam DedicationJune 4, 195Fair Oaks, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-93
      - Agricultural Legislation, Broadcast McClatchy Broadcasting Co.6-9-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-94
      - Sloughhouse Barbecue, Broadcast KFBF6-9-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-95; not recd
      - Interview with Virgil Pinkley on Alcoholic Beverage Control6-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-96; No material in file for this binder.
      - Legislation, Television KCCC-TV6-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-97
      - CSEA 14th Annual Institute on Government6-10-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-98
      - 770 on Television6-12-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-99; No material in file for this binder.
        Hollywood
      - National Convention of Edison Electric Institute6-13-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-100
      - Elks Flag Day6-13-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-101
      - Recordings on Governor's Traffic Safety Committee6-15-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-102; No material in file for this binder.
      - United Nations General Assembly6-20-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-103
      - 35th Annual Department Encampment Veterans of Foreign Wars6-22-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-104
      - Navy Swearing-In Ceremony6-22-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-105; No material in file for this binder.
      - KQED-TV Statement on Capital Punishment6-23-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-106
      - American Legion Boys State Inaugural6-23-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-107; No material in file for this binder.
      - Recording, Professional Photographers6-27-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-108; No material in file for this binder.
        Assn. Sacramento
      - American Legion State Convention6-28-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-109
      - Dinner honoring Dr. von KleinSmid6-28-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-110; No material in file for this binder.
      - Teamsters Dinner & Labor Show6-30-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-111; 12 items
      - Kiwanis Club7-6-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-112
      - International Association of Insurance Counsel7-7-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-113
      - Disneyland7-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-114
      - Numbered by Mistake, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-115
      - Bohemian Grove Talk7-29-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-116; 5 items
        Lakeside
      - National Governors' Conference8-9/12-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-117
        Chicago, Illinois
      - National Medical Association8-9-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-118; Los Angeles
        (Judge Nix rep. Governor)
      - Southern Pacific Centennial Dinner8-9-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-119; (Lt. Gov. Powers rep. Gov.)
      - Air Force Association Natl. Convention and Air Power Panorama8-13-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-120; (Lt. Gov. Powers rep. Gov.)
      - Am. Fed. of Labor Convention8-15-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-121
      - American Hellenic Educational Progressive Association--29th Convention8-17-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-122; (Lt. Gov. Powers rep. Gov.)
      - USC Summer Session8-23-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-123
      - Review of 40th Armored Division8-20-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-124
        Camp Roberts
      - UCLA School of Medicine Dinner for Directors8-24-55, Accession no. M0244; Speech No. 5-125